[
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_1",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "an exam",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_2",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a party",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_3",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a meeting",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_4",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a wedding",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "h"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_5",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a conference",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "f"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_6",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a class",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_7",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a sports event",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "g"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_8",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "matching",
    "question": "a play",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f", "g", "h"],
    "descriptions": {
      "a": "useful information or advice",
      "b": "a test to show what a person knows or can do",
      "c": "the time you go to bed",
      "d": "the most difficult",
      "e": "quiet",
      "f": "a person who listens",
      "g": "making a lot of noise",
      "h": "doing something"
    },
    "answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_9",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "The guest in the studio is a teacher.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_10",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "Some people can sleep well with a television on.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_11",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "It is bad to think a lot before going to bed.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_12",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "It is good to play video games before bed.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_13",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "It is good to turn your mobile off when you go to sleep.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1_lis_14",
    "level": "A1",
    "skill": "listening",
    "type": "true-false",
    "question": "It is bad to play loud music while you sleep.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "True"
  }
]
